PROFILE

being enthusiastic and passionate to Computer Engineering, Finance, Art, Education, art, meditation and travel

- -Representative at Sydney Rose IELTS since 2014
- -Popular investor at ETORO
- -Analyst at GoldenPiggy Investment
- -The top 1% local guide at Google Map (total 3.9 million viewed)
- -Top 10% popular reviewer at Google (total 194,000 viewed)

-0.0003% Top trader at ETORO

(60 traders out of 2 million users in globe) first appointed questioner to a billionaire Yoni Assia at Value Investing Berkshire Hathaway AGM conference (2021.May.2nd)



2021

ADDRESS

✓ 10help Street, chatswood 2067

✓ 80 waterloo rd, macquarie park 2113

EMAIL

ahrumnoh@gmail.com goldenpiggyinvestment@gma il.com

PHONE

0421 902 972

EXPERIENCE

2019 - present ETORO

A popular investor



- Trading US stocks, commodities and indices
- Managing fund of copiers to make profit, monthly basis as a swing trader
- Based on insight, trying to make a strategy

2019

2017

MACQUARIE UNIVERSITY

2020 - present

GOLDENPIGGY INVESTMENT

An analyst & columnist



- Providing insight of global economy, global politics and social issues
- Predicting some future financial stream based on insight and global news
- -Writing a column monthly basis for copiers and followers

2014- present

SYDNEY ROSE ENGLISH & IELTS



Teacher

- -Managing all curriculum and handling individual's learning ability.
- -letting them achieve their goal
- -good leadership, motivator, mentor

EDUCATION

2021 THE UNIVERSITY OF

SYDEY

CODING BOOTCAMP

PROEFFIONAL ACCOUNTING

MEGA INSTITUTE

ADVANCED MARKETING